Hisham Khatib Collection - Mediterranean Pilgrimage Association Resource AD_MC_030_ref150
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
Hisham Khatib Collection - Mediterranean Pilgrimage Association
1880s-1920s
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
Khatib, Hisham, Mr.
AD_MC_030_ref150
4 paige_boxes
2,789 Photographic Prints 22 albums, remainder loose prints.
Generally good, some brittle and warped.
Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150
Content Description
2,930 photographs and postcards (both individual prints and contained within albums) focussed on the Near East, including the Holy Land, Palestine, Jordan, Turkey, Syria and Egypt as well as a very small number from Europe.
Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Palestine; Jordan; Egypt; Syria; Lebanon; Landscapes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Postcards; Khatib, Hisham, Mr.
- Front cover, Circa 1928; 150_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- Inside cover: Boat plan and sample menu from the Mediterranean Pilgrimage association, SITMAR line - Societa Italiana di Servizi Marittimi., 27 April 1928; 150_000002; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Boats/Ships; Food; Advertisements; Newspaper Clippings; English Writing; Italian Writing
- (blank page), Circa 1900-1928; 150_000003; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- Tram Services and Excursions from Parker's Hotel, Naples., Circa 1928; 150_000004; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  English Writing; French Writing; Newspapers/Magazines; Public transportation
- Map of Naples from Parkers Hotel and Entrance Ticket to Solfatara., April 1928; 150_000005; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Italy; English Writing; Maps; Italian Writing
- Advertisement for L. La Duca & C. Catania., 1927; 150_000006; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Advertisements; Italian Writing; English Writing; Catania, Italy
- Postcard of the elephant and obelisk in Catania., Circa 1927; 150_000007; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Italy; Elephants; Animals; Fountains; Statues; Postcards; Photographic Prints; Catania, Italy
- Postcards of the lighthouse and Ras-el-Tin Palace in Alexandria., Circa 1928; 150_000008; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Lighthouses; Buildings; Architecture; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; English Writing; Mediterranean Sea; Photographic Prints; Palace; Ras El Tin Palace
- Two postcards of Alexandria harbour., Circa 1928; 150_000009; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Individual Portraits; Men; Hats; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Seas; Ports; Mediterranean Sea; English Writing
- Two postcards of Mohamed Ali Square and the French Gardens, Alexandria., Circa 1928; 150_000010; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Carriages/Coaches; Palm Trees; Men; Animals; Horses; Traditional Dress; Streets/Roads
- Postcards of the Majestic Hotel and general view of Alexandria., Circa 1928; 150_000011; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Women; Palm Trees; Streets/Roads
- Postcards of the El Nabi Daniel Mosque and Fort Napoleon in Alexandria., Circa 1928; 150_000012; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Men; Women; Traditional Dress; Carriages/Coaches; Children; Street Vendors; Shops; Mosques; Religious Sites; Nabi Daniel Mosque; Islamic Architecture
- Postcards of the railway station and Nubar Pasha monument in Alexandria., Circa 1928; 150_000013; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Train Station/Railway Station; Men; Street Lamps; French Writing; Clocks/Watches; Statues; Monuments; Pasha
- A postcard of Sherif Pasha Street in Alexandria., Circa 1928; 150_000014; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Architecture; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; Streets/Roads; Men; Women; Buildings; Cars; Transportation; English Writing; Shops; Street Lamps
- Postcards of the Antoniades Garden and general view of Alexandria., Circa 1928; 150_000015; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; Men; Traditional Dress; Hats; Buildings; Gardens; Palm Trees; Parks; Date Palms
- A postcard of the San Stefano Hotel and Casino in Alexandria., Circa 1928; 150_000016; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; English Writing; Hotels; Casinos; Buildings; Architecture; Palm Trees; San Stefano, Alexandria, Egypt
- Postcards of the Alexandria Exchange and El Mahmoudiyah canal., Circa 1928; 150_000017; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Architecture; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Carriages/Coaches; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; Men; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Street Lamps; English Writing; French Writing; Arabic Writing; Column/Colonnade; Traditional Dress; Canals; Water
- Postcards of Mohammed Ali Square and Pompey's Pillar in Alexandria., Circa 1928; 150_000018; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Carriages/Coaches; Streets/Roads; Alexandria, Egypt; Egypt; Men; Buildings; Architecture; English Writing; Palm Trees; Column/Colonnade; French Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues; Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Transportation; Roman Architecture
- (Blank page), Circa 1900-1928; 150_000019; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- Postcards of the Nubar Pasha monument and panoramic view of Alexandria., Circa 1928; 150_000020; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Alexandria, Egypt; Statues; Buildings; Architecture; Egypt; English Writing; Men; Monuments
- Two postcards of Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000021; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Cairo, Egypt; Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; English Writing; Mosques; Religious Sites; Monuments; Mosque of Muhammad Ali Pasha; Citadel, Cairo, Egypt; Islamic Architecture
- Postcards of the interior of a Coptic church and Mamluk tombs in Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000022; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Egypt; Cairo, Egypt; Tombs; Churches; Religious Sites; Monuments; Buildings; Architecture; Interiors; Religious Imagery; Men; Turban; Traditional Dress; Saint Virgin Mary's Coptic Orthodox Church (Hanging Church); Cemeteries; Islamic Architecture
- Postcards of tombs of the Caliphs, an obelisk and street scene in Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000023; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Monuments; Tombs; Cairo, Egypt; Egypt; Column/Colonnade; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Animals; Horses; Carriages/Coaches; Buildings; Architecture; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Men; English Writing
- Postcards of the Blue Mosque and Citadel in Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000024; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Citadel, Cairo, Egypt; Cairo, Egypt; Egypt; Mosques; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Islamic Architecture; Carriages/Coaches; Transportation; Animals; Donkeys; Men; Children; Traditional Dress; Mosque of Muhammad Ali Pasha; Street Lamps
- Three postcards of Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000025; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Cairo, Egypt; Egypt; Citadel, Cairo, Egypt; Religious Sites; Mosques; Streets/Roads; Animals; Donkeys; Nile River; Palm Trees; Rivers; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Children; Traditional Dress; Pyramids; Pyramids of Giza; Monuments; Mosque of Muhammad Ali Pasha; Islamic Architecture
- A Postcard of Opera Square in Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000026; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Statues; Monuments; Column/Colonnade; Buildings; Architecture; Street Lamps; Streets/Roads; Animals; Individuals (Persons); Carriages/Coaches; Transportation; Ataba, Cairo, Egypt
- Two postcards of Giza, Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000027; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Giza, Egypt; Egypt; Pyramids; Pyramids of Giza; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Men; Traditional Dress; Animals; Camels; Monuments; Statues; Ancient Egyptian Architecture
- Two postcards of Giza, Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000028; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Egypt; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; Pyramids of Giza; Monuments; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; Men; Traditional Dress; Turban; Animals; Camels; English Writing; Statues; Ancient Egyptian Architecture
- Two postcards and newspaper clipping of the Sphinx and the Pyramids, Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000029; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Giza, Egypt; Egypt; Pyramids; Pyramids of Giza; Monuments; Statues; English Writing; Ancient Egyptian Architecture
- Two postcards of Pyramids in Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000030; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Pyramids; Giza, Egypt; Palm Trees; Pyramids of Giza; Monuments; Men; Children; Animals; Camels; Buildings; Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Architecture; English Writing
- Postcards of Kasr el Nil bridge and the Pyramids., Circa 1928; 150_000031; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Giza, Egypt; Egypt; Palm Trees; Monuments; Pyramids; Pyramids of Giza; Bridges; Animals; Camels; Carriages/Coaches; Transportation; Men; Turban; Traditional Dress; Nile River; Rivers; English Writing; Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Cairo, Egypt
- Postcards of the barracks at Kasr el Nil and a wedding., Circa 1928; 150_000032; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Cairo, Egypt; Egypt; Nile River; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Rivers; Animals; Camels; Men; Turban; Traditional Dress; Buildings
- Postcards of Azhar University and a coffee house in Cairo., Circa 1928; 150_000033; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Cairo, Egypt; Egypt; Men; Group Portraits; Tea/Coffee; Turban; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Shisha/Hookah/Nargiles; Buildings; Column/Colonnade; Hats; Universities; Al Azhar University/Jāmiʻat al-Azhar
- Postcards of the Holy Carpet (Mahmal) procession and the pyramids., Circa 1928; 150_000034; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Cairo, Egypt; Egypt; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids of Giza; Pyramids; Animals; Camels; Men; Boys; Children; Monuments; Nile River; Rivers; English Writing; Mosques; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture; Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Mosque-Madrassa of Sultan Hassan; Islamic Architecture
- Postcards of men working on a shadoof and a Pharaonic statue., Circa 1928; 150_000035; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Men; Boys; Children; Cairo, Egypt; Egypt; Statues; Workers; Hats; Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Palm Trees; English Writing
- Postcards of women and children and Mosque of Mohamed Ali., Circa 1928; 150_000036; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Individual Portraits; Group Portraits; Women; Hijab (Islamic clothing); Children; Traditional Dress; Mosques; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Interiors; English Writing; Mosque of Muhammad Ali Pasha; Islamic Architecture
- Map of the Nile River., Circa 1928; 150_000037; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Maps; Nile River; Rivers; English Writing
- (Blank page), Circa 1900-1928; 150_000038; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- Postcard of a Nile Steamer named 'Arabia'., Circa 1928; 150_000039; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Nile River; Rivers; Hills; Buildings; Landscapes; Egypt
- Postcard of the Tomb of Tutankhamen., Circa 1928; 150_000040; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Thebes, Egypt; Egypt; Men; Doors/Entrances; Tombs; Monuments; Postcards
- A photograph and postcard of Jerusalem., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000041; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Streets/Roads; French Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Buildings; Individuals (Persons); Animals
- Three postcards of monuments in Jerusalem., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000042; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Buildings; Architecture; Chandeliers; Interiors; Religious Sites; Churches; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Palestine; Caves
- A postcard of the Church of Holy Sepulchre., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000043; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Jerusalem; Palestine; Interiors; Churches; Religious Sites; Religious Imagery; Chandeliers; Architecture
- Three postcards of the interior of the Church of Holy Sepulchre., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000044; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; French Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Churches; Religious Sites; Religious Imagery; Interiors; Chandeliers; Statues; Architecture; Jerusalem; Palestine
- Postcards of the Church of Holy Sepulchre and the Tower of Antonia., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000045; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Photographic Prints; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Churches; Religious Sites; Interiors; Buildings; Architecture; Jerusalem; Palestine; English Writing; French Writing; Italian Writing; Children; Men; Traditional Dress; Spanish Writing; Towers; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
- A postcard of the Arch of Ecce Homo., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000046; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Photographic Prints; Men; Animals; Traditional Dress; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Streets/Roads; Jerusalem; Palestine; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
- Postcards of the Dome of the Rock and the Jordan River., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000047; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Albumen Prints; Religious Sites; Dome of the Rock; Jordan; Rivers; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Men; Traditional Dress; Horses; Architecture; Buildings
- Postcards of the Valley of Jehoshaphat and Al Aqsa Mosque., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000048; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Jerusalem; Palestine; Mountains; Buildings; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Architecture; Al-Aqsa Mosque; Mosques; Islamic Architecture
- Postcards of Tombs of the Kings and Damascus Gate., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000049; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Jerusalem; Damascus Gate, Jerusalem; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; Tombs; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Animals; Donkeys; Horses; Men; Traditional Dress; Turban
- Postcards of the interior of the Dome of the Rock and the Tomb of the Virgin Mary., Circa 1900-1928; 105_000050; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Jerusalem; Postcards; Albumen Prints; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture; Column/Colonnade; Kidron Valley; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Tombs; Churches; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Men; Traditional Dress
- Postcards of the Tower of David and Hippicus, and the Golden Gate., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000051; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Tower of David; Jerusalem; Palestine; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture; Monuments; Golden Gate, Jerusalem; French Writing; English Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing
- Two postcards of the Garden of Gethsemane., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000052; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Gardens; Jerusalem; Palestine; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Men; Traditional Dress; Buildings; Architecture; Mountains
- Postcards of the Church of the Pater Noster and Mount Zion., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000053; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Albumen Prints; Jerusalem; Palestine; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Churches; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture; Mount Zion/Jabal Sahyoun (Jerusalem); Men; Traditional Dress; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Landscapes; Church of the Pater Noster
- Postcards of the Mount of Olives, Chapel of the Ascension, and the Cenacle., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000054; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Jerusalem; Palestine; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Religious Sites; Column/Colonnade; French Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing; English Writing; Hills; Architecture; Monuments; Chapel of the Ascension
- Postcards of the Abbey of the Dormition and Ein Karem., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000055; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Jerusalem; Palestine; Religious Sites; Churches; Buildings; Architecture; Mount Zion/Jabal Sahyoun (Jerusalem); French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Men; Italian Writing
- Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Front cover of a booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056a; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056b; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056c; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056d; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; Jerusalem; English Writing; Palestine
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056e; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056f; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Palestine; Jerusalem; Architecture; Photographic Prints
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056g; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Architecture; Photographic Prints
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056h; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056i; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Religious Sites
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056j; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Maps; Jerusalem; Palestine
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056k; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books
  - Booklet entitled "The Threshold of the Judgement Gate on the Place of the Russian Excavations in Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000056l; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057a; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Dome of the Rock
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057b; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057c; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057d; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Dome of the Rock; Jerusalem; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; Monuments; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057e; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057f; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; Palestine; Jerusalem; Dome of the Rock; English Writing
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057g; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Jerusalem; Sabil/Sebil; Dome of the Rock; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites; Buildings; Palestine
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057h; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057i; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Dome of the Rock; Column/Colonnade; Architecture; Buildings; Religious Sites